module.exports = {
  decks: [
    {
      id: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      title: 'animals',
    },
    {
      id: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      title: 'food',
    },
  ],
  cards: [
    {
      back: 'cat',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'قطّة (ج) قطط',
      id: '3e6b1142-721f-4282-a5c9-4d386af75db1',
    },
    {
      back: 'كلب (ج) كلاب',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'dog',
      id: 'c33d0964-e493-4774-b06f-3a3d33713530',
    },
    {
      back: 'بقرة (ج) بقرات',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'cow',
      id: 'e2c1938a-d8e8-4dff-afe2-f8a06e32481b',
    },
    {
      back: 'ثور (ج) ثيران',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'bull, ox',
      id: '258c8000-da01-4739-be4c-162287ee95d7',
    },
    {
      back: 'عجل (ج) عجول',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'calf',
      id: '45effaea-a706-425f-8d2e-81c248d1cd4e',
    },
    {
      back: 'جاموس (ج) جواميس',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'buffalo',
      id: 'd6433659-78fd-481e-9a0b-0be69e6aacab',
    },
    {
      back: 'بهيمة (ج) بهائم',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'cattle, livestock',
      id: '3bba0706-b0ae-4898-994f-063d9a3e581e',
    },
    {
      back: 'غنم (ج) أغنام',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'sheep',
      id: '304cfbb3-fef8-483d-acf3-9f3c16fe93fc',
    },
    {
      back: 'خروف (ج) خراف',
      deck: '81db73a9-ff7a-4d73-8902-ac9f4daa6ca3',
      front: 'lamb',
      id: '4a6ec85f-463d-4464-8933-d2796263cd70',
    },
    {
      back: 'ماء',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'water',
      id: '18e74cbb-96fe-4d20-96e8-0d6d6bcea571',
    },
    {
      back: 'شاي',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'tea',
      id: 'bcb80824-f20a-4a03-8c8f-cf20b71279e4',
    },
    {
      back: 'قهوة',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'coffee',
      id: 'f9200811-43a0-42bf-bbe6-ad84d603a457',
    },
    {
      back: 'حليب',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'milk',
      id: 'ceb633d9-827f-4656-ad25-10aeb2bd22e6',
    },
    {
      back: 'خمر',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'alcohol',
      id: 'a6465aa0-1197-4a49-a90d-24ed69b6ee3c',
    },
    {
      back: 'نبيذ',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'wine',
      id: 'a5b47dc8-f434-43ea-b733-005f266870bf',
    },
    {
      back: 'شامبنية',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'champagne',
      id: '2a7dce1a-97e8-4b55-bbd8-b9f2d3ea91eb',
    },
    {
      back: 'بيرة',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'beer',
      id: '8d2da5d7-caf5-449e-9d32-38e31e4ad092',
    },
    {
      back: 'فاكهة (ج) فواكه',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'fruit',
      id: '137cdf32-f643-4cb7-9506-dc5da57d86a9',
    },
    {
      back: 'تفّاح',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'apple',
      id: '091e1c59-c04c-4d69-bfc0-7525eb57ec94',
    },
    {
      back: 'برتقال',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'orange',
      id: '67799f66-5587-48cb-ab11-32a1a4585af2',
    },
    {
      back: 'موز',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'banana',
      id: '5d8e6ad6-2c17-43d2-abf1-9375129bb3c2',
    },
    {
      back: 'ليمون',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'lemon',
      id: '2d008871-a04d-4c3a-a6e9-254afe1f1242',
    },
    {
      back: 'ليمون حامض',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'lime',
      id: '44b713a5-cdd1-4475-a15d-d97aeb3e674a',
    },
    {
      back: 'بطّيخ',
      deck: '893ee4c6-7ad5-44b2-9345-231c607b737e',
      front: 'watermelon',
      id: 'f1df9c73-7bfa-4e6b-a167-edd3cbd59619',
    },
  ],
};
